-伊丽莎白 -看这里 -请看这里 -伊丽莎白 -我们爱你 -我们爱你
-Elizabeth -Over here -Look here please -Elizabeth -We love you -We love you
你能行！
You got it!
感受那股力量女士们
feel that power, ladies!
记住，膝盖要压下去，你可以的
And mark, get those knees down, you got it!
一起来
Come on!
踢臀！转身！
Butt! Hip!
没错，你做得很好
Oh yeah, you got it!
挺直，想象你穿着比基尼泡在海水里，你想
Square! Think about those bikini bathes you wanna...
看着像只沙滩上的水母一样
look like a giant jellyfish on the beach
继续
Come on!
伸展
Push!
你可以的，坚持住女士们，你们能行！
You got it! Hang in there ladies, you got it!
你可以的！
You got it!
锻炼完成，宝贝们！
Today's worked out baby!
好了我们下周见
All right then hope I'll see you next week
下次的《点亮你人生》我们将锻炼小腹部分
for Sparkle You Life, we 're gonna work on the latter labs
也是最难塑肌的部位
you know, the most difficult part to sculpts
与此同时，照顾好自己
but at the mean time, take care of yourselves
完事儿，一号位
work's fine, position one
干得漂亮！谢谢大家！
Great jobs,ladies!
大家辛苦了，很不错
-You got it! -Nice one
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
谢谢
thank you
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
哦，谢谢
Oh, thank you.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
谢谢
Thank you.
我不管你们是否要把镇上的小姑娘全找一遍
I don't care if every fucking young girl in the fucking town
几周内给我完成
in these few weeks.
听着，我说的很简单了
Look, I made it simple.
找年轻的
We need her young.
身材辣的
We need her hot.
马上去给我找
We need her now.
怎么能让那黄脸婆主持这么久
How the old bitch has been able to stick around for this long.
我他妈就不明白了
That's the fucking mystery to me.
哦得了吧，得过奥斯卡也得擦屁股滚蛋
Oh, Oscar winner, my ass.
再说得奥斯卡那是多少年前了？
When was that back in the 30s?
怎么，就因为一部《金刚》？
What, for King Kong?
不，鬼才记得给过她承诺
No, I don't give a fuck what we promised her.
这是网络电视节目
This is network TV,
不是傻逼慈善项目
not a fucking charity.
赶紧给我找新人
Find me somebody new.
快！
Now.
嘿，你知道女人25岁后就开始衰败了吗？
Hey, did you know that a woman's
fertility starts to decrease by the age of 25?
珍妮弗都几岁了？
How old is Jennifer?
你最好赶快
You better get busy.
伊丽莎白
她那老脸在电视上就跟屏幕上沾了屎一样
It's like when you see someone fart on screen.
人们喜欢的是美女
People just love that.
懂吗？这种节目就得小年轻干
I mean, that's just the way it is.
你能听懂吧？
So you know what I mean?
人的本性不会变
People are just people.
我就得按照人的本性来做
And I have to give people what they want.
股东也喜欢这么做
That's what keeps the shareholders happy.
而人们更是喜新厌旧
And people always ask for something new.
不得不换人
Renewal is inevitable.
等到了50岁
And at 50, well,
就绝经了
it stops.
绝什么？
What stops?
嗯？
What?
你说绝什么？
What stops?
额，你知道，就是
Um, you know, the um...
额……
The um...
哦，乔治！
Oh, George!
哦，哦！
Oh, oh!
-抱歉我得走了 -哈维！
-I'm sorry, I gotta run. -Harvey!
乔治！节目评价太赞了！
George! Those ratings are insane!
你真是天才
You're a genius!
哦，这有点乱
Oh, what a mess.
你太牛了
You're a genius.
所以才来庆祝
That's why you'd be drinking.
哦，太搞了
Oh, that's hilarious.
斯巴克女士，您走运了
Well, it's your lucky day, Miss Sparkle,
我们对您进行了全身扫描
because we have X-rayed you from head to toe,
您并没有任何牙隐裂
and you don't have so much as a crap molar.
您可以离开了
So, you are good to go.
额，疫苗已接种，ok
Uh, vaccination, okay?
没有度假计划
Not going on a vacation.
对了，我老婆，她是您的忠实粉丝
By the way, I just want to say, my wife is a huge fan.
额，血型……
Um, blood type...
哦，嘿，今天是您的生日
Oh, hey, it's your birthday.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
哦，是紧急呼叫，抱歉，我得去额……
Oh, uh, that's an emergency, I'm sorry. I, uh, had to have a...
再见
Bye.
稍等
One moment.
最后一项检查有点……
It's just one last exam to perform.
你刚才不是说我没事了吗
I thought he said I was good to go.
有问题吗？
Is there a problem?
没有，一切都很好
No, it's perfect.
您是我们的绝佳人选
You're a good candidate.
我是说，您要离开了吗
I mean, are you good to go?
祝您好运
I wish you the best.
“它改变了我的人生”
莉兹？
Lizzie?
莉兹 斯巴克？
Lizzie Sparkle?
天啊，不敢相信
Oh my God, I can't believe it.
费雷德
Fred!
十年级大课同班的弗雷德
Fred, from 10th grade homeroom!
哦，弗雷德，我当然记得
Oh, Fred, of course.
你真是一点没变啊
You haven't changed a bit.
还是这么美丽动人
You're still the most beautiful girl in the whole wide world.
知道吗，我跟随你进了同个行业
You know, I followed your career.
你可太成功了
What a success.
我是说，哇，哇，哇
I mean, wow, wow, wow.
哇
Wow.
嘿，不如我们一起去
Hey, why don't we go out
抽空喝几杯
maybe for a drink sometime
既然都，又遇见了，保持联系？
now that we're, you know, reconnected?
额……
Um...
哦，对，我的错
Oh, of course, I'm stupid.
你肯定很忙
You're super busy.
不过
But you know what?
不如你把名片给我
Why don't you give me your card?
还是说你，你没带……
I mean, you never help.
额，行，多可惜
Um, sure, what I...ah
这个体检单给你也行
This will do. Oh.
别看我的胆固醇指数，简直是场灾难
Don't look at my cholesterol levels. They're a disaster.
哦天啊
Oh, God.
这是啥？
What is that?
给吧
There.
现在你有我联系方式了
Now you've got it.
“感谢多年相伴！怀念往昔，那时的你太赞了！”
你有没有梦想过
Have you ever dreamt
成为华丽的自己
of a better version of yourself?
更年轻
Younger.
更美丽
More beautiful.
更完美
More perfect.
只需一次注射就能解放你的DNA
One single injection unlocks your DNA,
开始新的细胞分裂
starting a new cellular division
创造出另一个自己
that will release another version of yourself.
试试“某种物质”
This is the substance.
以你为基体
You are the matrix.
创造一切
Everything comes from you.
享有一切
And everything is you.
一个更华丽的自己
This is simply a better version of yourself.
只需相互分享
You just have to share.
一周是老的你
One week for one
一周是新的你
and one week for the other.
交替七天的完美平衡
A perfect balance of seven days each.
只需铭记
The one and only thing not to forget.
你们是一体的
You are one.
你无法躲避你自己
You can't escape from yourself.
喂？
Yes.
你好
Hello.
我想订购
I'd like to order.
地址
Address.
贝弗利峡谷街1057号
1057 Beverly Canyon.
来这个地方：北拜伦巷35号
Write this down: 35 North Byron Alley.
35号
35 North.
诚聘！
想成为下一个伊丽莎白斯巴克吗？
只要你年轻漂亮，秀色可餐，朝气蓬勃，就来吧！
年龄要求：仅限18-30周岁
“激活剂”
“一次性使用
用后即扔”
“稳定剂-完美体用”
“转换针”
“基体营养液”----“完美体营养液”
“你只能
激活一次”
“你必须每天
注射稳定剂”
“每七天转换一次
没有例外”
“铭记
你们是一体的”
以你为基体
You are the matrix.
创造一切
Everything comes from you
享有一切
and everything is you.
一个更加
This is simply
华丽的自己
better version of yourself.
你好
Hello.
谢谢
Thanks.
下周我们会通知你
We'll let you know by next week.
感谢
Thank you so much.
我很渴望这个机会
I'm just dying to get the part.
很棒的舞者
Great dancer.
嗯，可惜不能像看她脸一样直接看她那对奶子
Hmm, too bad her boobs aren't in the middle of her instead of the nose.
下一位！
Next!
这次感觉各方面都完美无瑕啊
Looks like everything sure is in the right place this time.
请告诉我们你的姓名，年龄，三围
Please say your name, age, measurements.
我叫苏
I'm Sue.
苏，苏，苏，苏，苏，苏，苏，苏，苏，苏，苏
Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue.
苏，苏，苏，苏，苏
Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue.
她在哪？
Where is she?
多么美艳的天使
What a gorgeous little angel.
你被录取了
You're hired.
我们的节目就需要你这样的人
We want a show that's just like you.
美丽快乐，蠢蠢欲动
Beautiful and happy.
人们都想开心
People want to be happy.
我们两周后开播，开始准备吧
We air in two weeks, so let's get to work.
剩下的交给我的助理就行
I'm gonna let you organize the rest with my assistant. uh...
-她叫…… -伊莎贝拉
-uh... -Isabella?
以-依-伊莎
Is-is-isis.
破名字念着都费劲对吧？
Who has time to say that?
以后就叫你辛迪得了
We're gonna make you Cindy.
名字更短，也更方便
It's shorter, it's better.
就这样，以后辛迪会给你安排详细，去做准备吧
So, I'm gonna let you organize everything else with Cindy.
哦，对了，走之前
Oh, um, before you go,
我有一个小问题
I just have to mention a...
关于我的行程安排
small scheduling issue.
我必须每隔一周去城外一趟
I have to be out of town every other week
照顾我母亲
to take care of my mother
她病得很严重
mother, who's very sick.
我只想要你来做这个节目
I want you for this show
你妈也好你，兄弟也好
and we will work around any mother, brother,
甚至你的阿猫阿狗也好，不管他妈生了什么病我们都能照顾好
fucking sick, puppy you need to take care of.
懂吗？
Hmm?
Hmm.
人美，还心地善良
Gorgeous, with a pure heart.
观众肯定会喜欢
People are gonna love that.
很好
Perfect.
“新人
新秀
即将推出”
跳跃，环胸，
So you jump out, touch your elbows,
低下头，拉伸
head down, contract.
五六七八，环胸
And five, six, seven, eight, elbows.
你去哪了？
Where have you been?
我一直想找你喝一杯给你送行
I've all been wanting to have a drink with you for your departure.
总而言之
Anyway,
我们额，众筹了下
we uh...all chipped in
给你准备了点小礼物供你消遣
and we got you just a little something to keep you busy.
这可是本法语书
It's French.
我老婆，她还为此生气了
My wife, she's for her spire.
哦，我可不想惹她
Oh, I don't want my wife.
糟了，我得走了
Oops, I gotta run.
很高兴要是还能再见到你
But it's always great to see you.
像羚羊和鹿角在你肌肤上移动
The antelope and the deer moving about
这可不是纸上谈兵
are going through the text.
这些按摩角还可远程操控.
The antelope with remotes.
竟然只卖49块9
I cannot believe the incredible price for $49.98.
混蛋，他们都要拿手机报警了，别弄噪音坏人事儿了！
God damn it, they have the phone and it's such a great night.
开门！
Open up.
快开门！
We gotta open up.
额，不好意思
And uh, sorry.
我以为是斯巴克那老太太
I thought that Ms. Sparkle.
她搬走了
She moved out.
我是新租客
I'm the new tenant.
苏
Sue.
奥夫
Olver.
奥利夫
Over.
奥利弗
Oliver.
你找我有事儿吗？
You wanted to complain about something?
奥利弗
Oliver?
怎么会？
What?
没事儿
No.
没没没没没没没
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
就是
I think it's
like awesome
感觉挺棒的
听着那些装修工具嗡嗡响，你能懂吗
when there's stuff going on in the building, you know what I mean?
额，事实上我还
Um, I'm actually,
我动手能力还挺强的，如果你需要帮忙
quite handy if you ever need,
或者需要各种援助、急救，额
need me to be of aid in any way. Ummm...
我一大袋子工具呢
I got a sack of tools and...
还有个大榔头
and a big hammer.
你懂我意思
You know what I mean.
总之，我也住这儿
Anyways, I live right here,
有需要就来找我
so you know where to find me.
Anytime.
随叫随到
不分昼夜
Day or night.
以后见
Later.
嗨各位
Hi everybody.
我是苏，是时候动起来啦
I'm Sue and it's time to pump it up.
准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
开始
Let's go.
感谢各位
Thank you so much everybody.
我们下周见
I'll see you next week.
与此同时
And in the meantime,
大家要保重哦
take care of yourself.
真有礼貌！
courtesy!
太绝了，太绝了
Wonderful, wonderful.
我不会待太晚，等我下
I won't be out late, so just wait for me.
别吃太快
Don't eat too fast.
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
没事，马上回来
Yes, I'll be right back.
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
你干什么去了？
What did you do?
你看着比之前还要美
You've seen me the more beautiful than before.
不
No.
“喝醉了不能骑摩托了，先留你这儿啦！:-）---特洛伊”
“和苏一起
动起来”
喂
Yes.
喂，你好
Yes, hi.
我是伊丽莎白 斯巴克
This is Elizabeth Sparkle.
503号
I'm 503.
请讲
Yes.
嗯你好
Yes, hi.
我用某种物质时没算好时间
There's been a slight misuse of the substance.
额外多用了一个小时
A few extra hours were accidentally used
结果手指额……变异了
causing umm... an alteration.
我想知道该怎么把它恢复原样
So I'm just looking for the procedure to reverse it.
另一个你消耗的时间到你身上就没了
What has been used on one side is lost on the other side
没办法补救
There's no going back.
不，我不知道她是怎么想的
No, I don't know what she was thinking.
而且显然她是喝醉了
And obviously she was drunk.
铭记没有你和她之分
Remember there is no she and you.
你们是一体的
You are one.
遵循平衡
Respect the balance
就不会有任何差错
and you won't have any more inconveniences.
你难道不知道，不知道，不知道，不知道
Don't you know, know, know, know
你难道不知道
Don't you know
你得动起来
You got to pump it up
你难道不知道，不知道，不知道，不知道
Don't you know, know, know, know
你难道不知道
Don't you know
你得动起来，动起来，动起来，动起来
You got to pump it up, pump it up, pump it up, pump it up
动起来，动起来，动起来
pump it up, pump it up, pump it up
你得动起来
You got to pump it up
苏！
Sue!
Sue?
我在电视上看见你了
I just saw you on TV.
我勒个去
Holy moly.
看得我想报你的班了
Makes me want to join your class.
嘿，你不开私教课对吗？
Hey, you don't give private lessons, do you?
嘿，额……
Hey, ummm...
要不要来我家里喝点酒？
What about a drink at my place tonight?
来啊，别害羞
Come on, don't be shy.
我知道你就站在门后，大美人
I see you standing behind the door there, gorgeous.
行吧
All right,
慢慢来，但记得我约了你哦
take your time, but it's a date.
你懂的，动起来
You know, pump it up
你得动起来
You got to pump it up
你懂的，动起来
You know, pump it up
你得动起来
You got to pump it up
苏
Sue.
来点什么？
What can I get you?
摩卡拿铁
Moka Latte.
很难熬对吗？
It's long, isn't it?
你说什么？
Excuse me?
七天很难熬
Seven days.
你跟踪我来的吗？
Did you follow me here?
我就是好奇
I was just curious
好奇你发生了什么
to find out how things were going for you.
每一次你都感觉更加
Each time you feel a little more...
孤独
lonely,
不是吗？
don't you think?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you were talking about.
我很好
I'm fine.
万事大吉
Everything's fine.
每一次都会更加困难
It gets harder each time
记住你还值得活在世上
to remember that you still deserve to exist.
再丑陋的你也是你
That this part of yourself
也有活着的意义
is still worth something
你还值得
that you still matter.
她已经开始了吗？
Has she started yet?
开始蚕食你了吗？
Eating away at you?
操！
Fuck!
小心点！
Watch out!
看什么？
What?
嘿！
Hey!
滚啊！
Move!
你还是那么美丽动人
You're still the most beautiful girl in the whole wild world.
你好？
Hello?
嗨，弗雷德
Hi, Fred.
我是莉兹
It's Lizzie.
喂？
Hello?
抱歉，我，我呆住了
Sorry, I mean, I'm a chalk.
哦
Oh.
哇
Wow.
哇，哇
Wow, wow.
我还以为永远都接不到你的电话了……
I thought I'd never hear from you again after-...
哦，天，别，不是，我只是，有点
Oh gosh, no, no, not at all. I just, I've just...
最近有点忙不开
I've just been really busy lately.
我想说，我在想
So listen, I was thinking that
我们有空可以一起聚一聚？
maybe we could get together and grab a drink?
你还在听吗？
Are you still there?
抱歉，我，我，我，我又惊呆了
Sorry, I'm, I'm, I'm in shock again.
那我定路易吉餐厅，八点行吗？
I could book Luigi's at eight?
八，八，那就八点路易吉餐厅见
Ei...Ei...Eight in Luigi's it is.
啊，我……我们晚上见
Uh I... I will see you tonight.
拜拜
Bye.
好的，拜
Okay, bye.
“弗雷德
我到餐厅了
你要迟到了吗
我知道你肯定想闪亮登场 :)
你还好吗？”
嗨，各位
Hi everybody.
嗨
Hi.
好了，我们开始，把台子清理一下
Okay, here we go everyone. Clear the set please.
第一机位，谢谢
First positions, thank you.
运镜开始
Roll cameras.
三，二，一
And in three, two, one.
下蹲，下蹲，下蹲
Squat, squat, squat.
屁股扭一圈
Circle those hips.
拉伸，拉伸，拉伸，拉伸，拉伸，拉伸
Contract, contract, contract, contract, contract, contract.
抱头下腰
head between your legs.
停
Cut.
不好意思，我以为，我以为，我
I'm sorry, I thought I, thought I, I,
我走神了
I just got distracted.
没关系，再回退一遍
Not a problem, let's get right back to it.
从一机位开始
Back to one please.
打扰一下，管理室找
Sorry, it's the control room now.
导演说他从监控器看到奇怪的东西
The director said he saw something bizarre on the monitor.
摄像机重播一下，二号位
Bring up the replay on camera two.
二号机
Camera two.
快进
Forward.
我能换上礼服吗？
Can I have my dressing gown?
抱歉，礼服在更衣室
Sorry, it's in your dressing room.
那你快去拿去啊！
Well go and and get it.
慢慢播，一帧一帧
Let's just take this frame by frame.
给我五分钟
I need five minutes.
喂
Yes.
平衡没效了
This balance is not working.
我压根没时间享受
I barely have anytime to enjoy myself
而她却能虚度七天
while she wastes seven days
整日把脸埋电视机里
stuffing her face in front of the TV.
铭记没有你和她之分
Remember there is no she and you.
爱你们
I love everybody.
怎么了？
What's happening?
大家去哪了？
Where is everybody?
节目取消了
The TV's been canceled.
-什么？为什么？ -苏
-What, why? -Sue.
哈维要你马上去办公室见他
Harvey wants to see you in his office immediately.
知道了
Okay.
我会让他改变主意
I'll go change him.
不，他让你马上去
No, he said now.
我就开门见山了
I'll get right to the bond.
你不能一直做早间节目
We can't keep you on the morning show.
为什么？我才刚做起来
But why? I just started.
收视率登顶了
Ratings are through the roof.
我们从42点开始
We started at 42.
一路飙升到现在大概
Now we're up to like--
216点
216.
现象级的成功
It's phenomenal!
大家喜欢你
People love you!
爱慕你
They adore you.
他们想看更多更多的你
They want more and more and more of you.
所以我们决定
That is why we have decided
你将作为主持
that we want you
主持今年的跨年演出
to host the New Year's Eve show.
你你你你你是说……
Yoooou mean the...
电视网最大的演出
The network's biggest show.
五千万人在线观看
50 million viewers live.
你甚至能收视更高
You can't go higher than that.
但时间紧迫
That's gonna be intense.
只有一两个月时间准备
We only have a few months to pull it off, so,
你愿意吗？
are you in?
只有你给运气开了门
If you don't open the door and opportunity knocks,
你才能有机会抓住它
you won't get another chance.
你们都知道这点
You of all people know this.
就再要一天，然后剩下的七天交给你
Just one more day and then I have a whole week off.
我们换回来
We can switch.
我们得去拍《时尚》杂志的封面写真
We're doing the cover of Vogue.
就再多一天，行吗？
Just one more day, okay?
-是的 -她没有遵守平衡
-Yes.  -She didn't respect the balance.
她窃取了我更多的时间
She's stealing more and more time from me,
压根不计后果
completely without consideration of the consequences.
她就是个自私的婊子
She's a selfish bitch.
那你要终止吗？
Would you like to stop?
终止
Stop.
你是基体
You are the Matrix.
如果你不满意
If you are not satisfied,
你可以终止体验
you can put an end to the experience
重回自己本身
and go back to being just you on your own.
确定要终止吗？
Would you like to stop?
我会回到之前的样子吗？
Will it go back to the way it was before?
已经转换的无法返还
What has been transferred won't come back,
但你可以终止体验
but you can stop the experience.
现在，你还要终止吗？
As of now, would you like to stop?
重回自己本身
To go back to being just you on your own?
不
No.
不，不，不
No, no, no.
不能终止
I can't stop.
只是她……
She just--
必须要遵循平衡
The balance just needs to be respected.
那就遵循平衡
So respected.
停下，停下，停下，停下，停下
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it.
你是赢家
You are the winner.
恭喜，你已经赢得了2万5千美元奖金
Well, congratulations, you've won $25,000.
我们还有最后一关
We'll have one final chance
一个问答题
a simple question
答对了就能再进一步，或得25万美元
in our big question round and play for $250,000.
而这道题你只有45秒的时间作答……
And you'll have just 45 seconds to come up...
操
Fuck.
老板
Boss.
是的，女士们先生们，她来了！
Yes, ladies and gentlemen, she is here.
今日顶流女星，苏！
The superstar of the moment, Sue.
准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
掌声有请，苏！
Let's welcome her, Sue.
你像不知哪冒出来的龙卷风一样席卷所有萤幕
You popped up nowhere on our screens like a tornado.
谁都没有预料到你的出现
I don't think anybody was really prepared for this world.
从早间节目升起的新星
It all started with the morning show
有传言称你会参演汤姆格兰特的下一部电影
and rumor has it that you are up for Tom Grant's next movie.
稍等片刻
Wait, just a moment.
我被告知你将主持今年的跨年晚会
I'm being told that you are going to host the New Year's Eve show.
你能证实这个消息吗？
Can you confirm this?
是的，没错
Yes, that's right.
我的天啊，重大新闻
Oh my God, that is huge news.
跟我们聊聊你自己吧
Tell us a little bit about yourself.
你家是哪的？
Where are you from?
怎么被挖掘出来的？
How did you get discovered?
我想知道，我们所有人都想知道你的一切
I want, we want to know everything.
其实，我也没什么能说的
Well, I mean, there's really not very much to tell.
毕竟只是一个
I'm just a girl from a
从印第安纳州走出来的小女孩
very small town in Indiana.
我家的小镇你们都不一定听说过
I'm sure that you've never heard of it.
事实上，连个镇子都算不上
In fact, it's not even a town.
我都不确定它算不算得上村子
I'm not sure you could really even call it a village.
一个农场，可以吗？
It's a farm, perhaps?
但从我记事起
But ever since I can remember,
登上萤幕就是我的梦想
it has always been my dream to be on screen.
我的梦想才对
This is my dream.
小时候，我会表演节目给家人看
As a child, I used to put on shows for my family.
呃，你的家人
Mm, your family.
真贴心
How sweet.
那，大家都注意到你顶替了伊丽莎白斯巴克的位置
So, everyone is aware that you replaced Elizabeth Sparkle.
毫无疑问，你一脚插了进来
And no doubt about it, you stepped in,
还把收视率提高到了不同的量级
you turned up the volume,
风靡全世界
and you rocked their world.
那你原来是斯巴克的粉丝吗？
Were you a fan of her show?
额，我，我不能，额
Um, well, well, I can't, uh,
其实不能说我看过她的节目
I can't really say that I actually watched her show.
要知道我们毕竟压根是不同时代的人
You do know that we're not exactly from the same generation.
必须承认的是
And you have to admit, it
那些节目都老掉牙了
it was a bit old-fashioned.
简直是侏罗纪活化石
Jurassic Fitness, really.
它们的问题就是得与时俱进了
the problem is it needed a change.
我他妈要给你看看
I'll fucking show you.
你想看侏罗纪活化石？
You wanna see some Jurassic Fitness?
你想看？！
You want it?!
来啊，来看看你他妈的侏罗纪活化石
Come on, come get your fucking Jurassic Fitness!
但我母亲是她的铁粉
But my mother was a huge fan of hers.
所以每个大清早，晴天雨天
So, every morning, rain or shine,
她的《点亮你生活》都在电视上播放着
Sparkle, your life, was on TV.
所以一定程度上，我是和她一起成长的
So, in a way, I grew up with her.
不论我喜不喜欢
Whether I liked it or not.
可能这也是你这么说的原因
I guess that's why you could say
我们有着某种联系
we have some sort of connection.
某种联系
Some sort of connection.
没了我你压根就不存在
You wouldn't exist without me.
邦，邦，邦，邦，邦
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
时间到了，女士们先生们，最后一个问题
It is time, ladies and gentlemen,  for our final question.
也是我们每个人都想问
The question that we ask
-甚至每个嘉宾都要问的问题 -好的
-each and every one of our guests. -Okay.
你能和我们稍微分享一下你的美丽秘诀吗？
Would you share one of your little beauty secrets with us?
稍微一点点
Just one little trick of yours
你能保持如此美貌的秘诀
that helps you look so incredibly stunning.
你本人是多么漂亮
I mean, look at you.
我也不知道，就……
I don't know. Uh...
说出来
Say it!
让我想想
Let me think.
说出来
Say it!
告诉他们你的美丽秘诀
Tell them who your little beauty secret is!
-我想， -怎么不敢直接说啊？
-I guess, -why don't you just show them right here?
这就是你的美丽秘诀
Here's your little beauty secret.
我想我只是敢于做自己
I guess I just try to be myself.
真诚，感激自己拥有的一切
To be sincere and grateful for all that I have.
铭记随着自己的内心生活
And to always remember to live with my heart.
哦，甜进我心窝去了
Oh, I'm here at the sweetheart center.
我只是，嗯，哦，敢于做自己
I just, woo, oh, I try to be myself.
停下！
Stop it!
Stop it.
你从我这抢走了
You're taking it from me.
你的美是从我这抢走的
That's your little secret.
停下！停下！停下！停下！停下！停下！……
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!......
你必须克制你自己
You have to control yourself!
我回不去了，要是我终止……
I can't go back, if I turn....
哦
Oh.
恶心的老东西
Gross old rat.
停下！
Stop it!
“3个月后”
“跨年晚会
明晚9点”
“祝好运！观众会爱死你的”
上床吗？
Coming to bed?
好，马上来
Yes, I'll be right there.
喂
Yes.
嗨，嗨，紧急情况，我……
Hi, hi, this is emergency. There's a...
我没有稳定剂了
There's no more stabilizer fluid.
喂？
Hello?
我是他妈的503号
It's fucking 503.
知道
Yes.
操！
Fuck!
我说了这是紧急情况
I'm telling you, this is urgent.
我稳定剂用完了
There's no more stabilizer fluid.
那说明你到最后阶段了
It means you've reached the end.
你什么意思？
What do you mean the end?
你已经消耗完了
You've drained it all out.
如果你还想要更多，必须等它重生
If you want more, you must let the fluid regenerate.
告诉我该怎么做
Tell me how to do it.
我现在就需要稳定自己
I need to stabilize myself right now.
你只需要换回来就行
You simply have to switch.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
换回来后就能开始稳定剂恢复
The switch reboots the fluid secretion process
然后你便能继续体验
so you can continue to enjoy the experience.
不，不，不，不，不
No, no, no, no, no.
我不能转换，我不能
I can't switch, I can't.
尤其是现在
Especially not now.
你别无选择
There is no other option.
苏？
Sue?
宝贝？
Babe?
苏？
Sue?
你还好吗？
You all right?
要不我明天再来？
Should I start about tomorrow?
宝贝？
Babe?
苏？
Sue?
哪里不对劲吗？
Is something wrong?
你看起来有点暴躁不安，是工作的事儿吗？
You look cranky, because your related business?
苏，开下门
Sue, open the door.
快啊，苏？
Come on, Sue.
这不好玩，我也要小便
not funny, I need to take a pee.
苏，开门
Sue, open the door.
开门，苏，快开门
Open the door, Sue, come on.
开门，快开门
Open the door, come on.
什么玩意儿？
What the fuck?
给我滚开！
Get the fuck out!
你是谁？你他妈是谁？
Who's this? Who the fuck is that?
离我远点！
Leave me alone!
卧槽什么鬼？
What the fuck?
喂？
Yes?
我是503号
It's 503.
我想终止
I want to stop.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
一旦终止，便不能退回了
Once you stop, you can't go back.
我想要终止！我他妈要终止！
I want to stop! I want to fucking stop!
我要终止！
I want to stop!
我们知道了
We'll deliver.
“抱歉但您未能遵守平衡”
“终断剂”
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
一旦终止，便不能退回了
Once you stop, you can't go back.
你会保持你自己的模样
You will simply remain on your own.
重回自身
Just on your own.
重回自身，自身，自身，自身
Just on your own. on your own. on your own.
-他妈的闭嘴！ -自身
-Shut the fuck up! -Your own.
好了
Okay.
我不能……我做不到
I can't... I can't do this.
我需要你
I need you.
我需要我自己
I need myself.
你，你快，你得准备好。今晚是属于我们的
You, you got, you gotta get ready. It's our big night.
快啊，他们会特别爱你
Come on. They're gonna love you so much.
快啊
Come on.
快
你是我唯一被爱的部分，你必须醒过来
You're the only lovable part of me. You have to come back.
快醒过来，快点
You have to come back. Come back.
没事，没事
Okay. Okay.
快啊
Come on.
快
不要
Oh, don't!
“铭记
你们是一体的”
你们知道发生什么了吗，化妆组？
You guys know what happened, makeup?
这人，你得跟我们去隔间
Here, we gotta get you the pinning room.
还有最后一个舞台测试，灯光，音响
We have one final test on stage, of lighting and sound.
现在演出前我们留在外面
now we wait outside before show starts.
你看行吗？
You got it?
-嗯…… -没事吧？
-En... -You good?
没事，走吧
Okay, let's go.
真美
Grab it.
风韵十足
Wonderful.
准备惊艳全场吧
There you go.
还好吗？
You good?
你等会儿要跳舞吗，女士？
You gonna dance, lads?
抱歉我马上回来
I'm gonna be right back, sorry.
苏！他们要你去台上测灯光效果
Sue! They need to see you on stage to test the light.
你有没有梦想过
Have you ever dreamt
成为更华丽的自己
of a better version of yourself?
更美丽，更完美
More beautiful, more perfect.
苏？
Sue?
好的，我们舞台上见
Yes, let me meet you there.
没事，我们台上见
Okay, so I'll wait for you on stage.
苏？
Sue?
来见见我们的股东们
Let me introduce you to the shareholders.
他们对你期盼已久
They have been dying to meet you.
有什么问题……吗？
Is everything...okay?
那就微笑
So smile.
我们今晚就要你笑出来
That's what we want tonight.
尤物就该保持微笑
Pretty girls should always smile.
羽毛诱惑！羽毛诱惑！羽毛诱惑！
Feathers! feathers! feathers!
嘿，准备好了吗？
Hey, you ready for tonight?
你能成为更华丽的自己吗？
Would you be the better version of myself?
请让我更美丽，求求了！
Please give me a better version of myself, please!
求求了！
Please!
变美！
Come on!
这次感觉各方面都完美无瑕啊
Looks like everything sure is in the right place this time.
请告诉我们你的姓名，年龄，三围
Please say your name, age, measurements.
我叫……
I'm...
“怪物伊丽杀苏”
尤物就该保持微笑
Pretty girls should always smile.
可出来了，我们都等急了
At last, we're starting to worry.
快点，从五号机位前上台
Hurry up, you're up in five.
她来了，真美啊
There she is, so beautiful.
我们爱你
We love you.
这才是你的舞台
This is where you belong.
这永远都是你的舞台
You always belong here.
没有你我们什么都不是
We can't do it without you.
没有你我们一事无成
We'll never do it without you.
你会把所有人比下去
You are here to replace them all?
女士们，快，上台
Girls, come on, let's go.
还在等什么？
What are we waiting for?
-快啊！ -都快点，快走，快走
-come on! -Everybody, let's go, let's go, let's go.
你肯定不会失望
You will not be disappointed.
她可是我最美丽杰作
She's my most beautiful creation.
是我一手造就了她
I have shaped her for success.
五，四，三，二，一
Five, four, three, two, one.
“开播”
怪物！
The monster!
快杀了它！
Shoot the monster!
怪胎！
It's a freak!
快杀了它！
Shoot the monster!
-别怕-怪物！
-Don't be scared. -Monster!
是我啊！
It's still me!
是我！
It's me.
我是伊丽莎白，我是苏……
I'm Elizabeth, I'm Sue.
怪胎！
Freak!
怪胎，怪物，怪物！
Freak, monster, monster!
是我啊
It's me.
不，我只是……
No I'm just...
可惜不能像看她脸一样直接看她那对奶子
Too bad her boobs aren't in the middle of her face instead of that nose.
下一位！
Next!
尤物就该保持微笑
Pretty girls should always smile.
50岁后
at 50.
就绝经了
It stops.
真漂亮
So beautiful
我们爱你
We love you.